dailyblogtools.com 2018-12-22

# Privacy Policy | Daily Blog Tools

Thank you for visiting  **our web site.**  This  **Privacy policy**  tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed at any time, you are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Note:** the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

**Collection of Information**

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses

, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

**Cookies and Web Beacons.**

**http://www.dailyblogtools.com**  does not use cookies.

**http://www.dailyblogtools.com**  has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**Distribution of Information.**

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing Purposes.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least  **13 years old or older.**

**Commitment to Data Security.**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

**Privacy Contact Information.**

If you have any  **Questions, Concerns, or Comments**  about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

E-mail:  **Webmaster@dailyblogtools.com**  — **[Contact Us](http://dailyblogtools.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us")**
